Elisabeth Kubler-Ross, a Swiss psychologist who devoted her whole life to patients on the brink of death, once said this.
The most beautiful people I know are those who have experienced suffering, loss, fight and defeat, and who found their way out of their bottom.
These people have gratitude, sensitivity and understanding for life, which they fill with compassion, gentleness and deep love full of interest.
Beautiful people don't just appear like that.
If you are in the middle of a difficult period of life, this song is dedicated to you.
I found the way out of the depth, richer for paying the cost, of having a dream disappear, of finding a hope that will last.
Beautiful people don't happen overnight.
I found the way out of the depth, richer for paying the cost, of having a dream disappear, of having a dream disappear.
I didn't know how to forgive, things that I couldn't forget.
I wasn't ready to change, I hadn't felt love yet.
My self-righteousness was a wall, so when it came falling apart, freedom was found in the breaking of my heart.
I believe there is a place where we are fully who we were always meant to be.
How it happens, all I know is that no one gets there on a rainy street.
So if it feels like you're losing again and again, not one minute is wasted of that pain.
I believe there is a place where we are fully who we were always meant to be.
Kind and gracious, forgiving and patient, with compassion for the wounded and the weak.
How it happens, all I know is that no one gets there on a rainy street.
No one gets there on a rainy street.